imhosted.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy Policy, Service Policies - ImHosted.com

ImHosted understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your information is used and shared online. We strongly believe in individual's rights to privacy and that personal information is not a commodity and should not be treated as one. 

This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of our services and websites. This privacy policy does not cover how our customers/clients may use or share data that they collect using our services. Our websites and services may contain links to other third party websites. We have no control over how your data is collected, stored or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them. 

**Information We May Collect From You During Registration, Website Visits, Support or Use of Services**

Data that you provide during the sign-up/registration process to our services. This may include your name, company name, e-mail address, address, phone number, geographic location.

Data that you provide to us when contacting us for support via e-email or phone. This may include your name, e-mail address, service information and payment information for verification of your identity.

Data that you provide to us when making payment to us for our services provided. This may include your name, company name, e-mail address, address, phone number, geographic location and credit card data.

Data during your usage of our Websites/Supports and Services. This may include Operating System, browser, IP address, geographical location, clicks, page visits or data collected from cookies. If you contact us for support, we will typically keep a copy of that correspondence.

 **Uses of Your Information**

We use your information to provide the best possible services to you. This includes:

\- To provide and manage your accounts  
\- To provide, improve and ensure functioning services to you  
\- To respond to communication from you or assist with services support  
\- To improve our websites and services and your user experience  
\- To administrate our websites and services  
\- To communicate with you

Payment information that you provide to us, such as credit card information, will only be used to facilitate payment for our products and services.

 **How and Where Do We Store Your Data?**

Transmission of data information over the internet or website is not guaranteed to be completely secure and that you are advised to take suitable precautions when transmitting data to us. However, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and protect your information against unauthorized use, access, modification, destruction, loss or theft in accordance with legislative requirements. 

Information provided to us is stored on our or our subcontractors’ secure servers and subject to security policies and standards. 

We retain your personal information to provide services to you and for legal requirements. We will retain your information for as long as necessary for the processing purposes of the information collected. When the information is no longer needed or expiry of regulatory requirements regarding retention of such data, we will securely remove the data unless otherwise required by law or regulation to retain for information for extended time.

 **Sharing of Information**

We may contract with third parties to supply services to you on our behalf. This may include third party payment processors/vendors, fraud detection or domain services. In some cases, the third parties may require access to some of your data. Where any of your data is required for such a purpose, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your data will be handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, our obligations, and the obligations of the third party under the law. 

In certain circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain data held by us, which may include your personal information, for example, where we are involved in legal proceedings, where we are complying with the requirements of legislation, a court order, or a governmental authority. We do not require any further consent from you in order to share your data in such circumstances and will comply as required with any legally binding request that is made of us.

 **Business Reorganisation**

We may expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of our business. Data provided by users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use the data for the purposes for which it was originally collected by us.

 **Transfers outside of the EEA**

In order for us to provide the services to you, your personal information will be transferred to and stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Your personal information may also be accessed by staff outside the European Economic Area (EEA). We will safeguard your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Your Rights**

If you have any questions in relation to our use of your Personal Information, you should first contact us as per the “Contacting Us” section below. 

We will require you to verify your identity with information known only by the account holder to make sure you are entitled to exercise of the rights as per below. This may also be subject to certain exemptions to safeguard public interest or our interest. 

You may have the right to require us to : 

\- provide you with further information on data we hold about you, our usage of your information, information that you have previously provided to us, and who we share it with  
\- update any incorrect or incomplete personal information we hold of you  
\- delete any personal information where you believe it is no longer necessary for us to hold or that we no longer have a lawful ground to use  
\- object to any processing based on the legitimate interests ground unless our reasons for undertaking that processing outweigh your data protection rights  
\- restrict how we use your information whilst a complaint/issue is raised

 **Cookies**

Cookies are small data files stored on your computer that allow proper functionality of our websites and services. They allow us to record your information when you visit our websites/use our services. First party cookies are those placed directly by us and are used only by us. We use cookies to facilitate and improve your experience on our site and to improve our services provided to you. 

By accessing our website and services, you may also receive certain third party cookies on your computer or device. Third party cookies are those placed by websites, services, and/or parties other than us. 

Certain features of our website depend on cookies to function and are deemed as “strictly necessary”. These cookies let you navigate our websites and use essential features, including secure areas and shopping cart. We require these cookies to deliver proper functionality of our websites and services to you.

Our website uses analytical services. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse usage statistics, enabling us to better understand how people use website and services. This, in turn, enables us to improve our website and services offered through it. You do not have to allow us to use these cookies, as detailed below, however whilst our use of them does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of our websites and services, it does enable us to continually improve our website and services, making it a better and more useful experience for you.

You can choose to enable or disable cookies in your internet browser. Most internet browsers also enable you to choose whether you wish to disable all cookies or only third party cookies. By default, most internet browsers accept cookies but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser or the documentation that came with your device.

You can choose to delete cookies at any time however you may lose any information that enables you to access our website and services more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, login and personalisation settings.

It is recommended that you keep your internet browser and operating system up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser and manufacturer of your computer or device if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or request to changes to your privacy preferences and personal information, please contact us by email at corporate@imhosted.com. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time, or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on our website and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your continued use of our services following the alterations.
